I will not hold off...
zangou no ue nigeba wa nai
塹壕の上　逃げ場はない
I know that's what we want
I know it's a war we want!
All rise your guns warae, kurue!
All rise your guns 嗤え、狂え！
I know that's what we want
I know it's a war we want!
Coming up, coming up...
ahh, satsui no me
ahh, 殺意の目
iki na emono takaburu takaburu
活きな獲物　昂る 昂る
Not enough, not enough...
mada sono inochi
まだその命
yuuetsu da We must not hide!
優越だ We must not hide!
We honor the JINGOS!
kemonojimita yokubou musaboru
獣染みた欲望貪る
We are in the JUNGLE!
saa, kiba wo toge shi no kazu wo kisoou
さあ、牙を研げ 死の数を競おう
We honor the JINGOS!
We honor the JINGOS !
I know that's what we want
I know it's a war we want!
We are in the JUNGLE!
I know that's what we want
I know it's a war we want!